# BADIU IOANA ANDREEA

#### W E B D E V E L O P E R



## CONTACT

- +40 731 003 833
- badioana9898@gmail.com
- O Cluj-Napoca, Romania
- Portfolio Link
- Linkedin Link

#### ABOUT ME

Hello there!

I'd describe myself as patient, curious, creative and detail-oriented.

Professionally, I've worked with PHP (including Laravel) and Vue.js, but I'm more interested in frontend technologies, which is why I've spent my spare time learning React.

My main goal is to grow as a frontend developer while exploring more about UI/UX design and improving my web and graphic design skills on my own. On a personal note, I'm friendly, optimistic and believe you can work with passion and enjoy the process at the same time.

# WORKING EXPERIENCE

#### WEB DEVELOPER

Kunden Broker Companie de Brokeraj S.R.L., Cluj-Napoca 09/2024 - Present

- · Developed an application for sending bulk email messages.
- Tech stack: PHP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL.
- Implementing cron jobs for scheduling email dispatch.
- Utilizing libraries such as PHPMailer, PHPSpreadsheet and TCPDF.
- Creating multiple email templates and scheduling functionality.
- Designing and building an admin panel for automating email sending.

#### WEB DEVELOPER

Roweb Development S.R.L, Pitesti

09/2019 - 12/2023

- Implement responsive design using CSS3, SCSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Vue.js.
- Create a style guide for general components using CSS.
- Working with vanilla PHP for a custom CMS platform and be familiarized with Laravel framework.
- Make improvements to deprecated code, develop reusable components and fix bugs.
- Have experience with consuming RESTful APIs.
- Implement and execute SEO improvements.
- Have experience in optimizing web pages with Google Page Speed.
- Work with Google Analytics to migrate from Universal Analytics (UA) to GA4.

- Utilize the Tag Manager platform to create custom events and GA4 events, including Page View tracking integration into the website's code.
- Use Bitbucket and GitHub for version control.
- Possess basic knowledge in Linux and Docker usage.
- Perform manual testing and cross-browser testing on web pages.
- Provide technical support for software applications.
- · Working with MYSQL database

### **EDUCATION**

#### **BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN INFORMATICS**

University of Pitesti, Department of Mathematics and Informatics

2017 - 2020

- Training at Prodinf Software: Java applications, Oracle database.
- Internship at Roweb Development: Introduction to the Laravel framework.
- Web application workshop.
- Bachelor's thesis topic: Data Management System for a Private Kindergarten (technologies used: Laravel, MySQL, Bootstrap, CSS & HTML, Email Delivery Platform).
- Graduated with a Bachelor's Degree, earning a grade of 10.

## **ERASMUS+ SCHOLARSHIP FOR ONE SEMESTER**

Vilnius University, Faculty of Mathematics and Informatics, Lithuania

2018-2019

Studied subjects: Database Management System, Human-Computer Interaction, Algorithm Theory,
 Numerical Methods for Differential Equations, Programming Windows API and Lithuanian Language

#### HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, MATHEMATICS - INFORMATICS PROFILE

Ion C. Bratianu National College, Pitesti

2013-2017

Grade on the baccalaureate exam: 9.28.

## TECH STACK & TOOLS

- JavaScript (Vue.js, React.js, jQuery)
- · CSS, SCSS, HTML
- Bootstrap
- REST API
- PHP (Laravel / Lumen, YII)
- MySQL
- CMS, Wordpress
- GitHub & Bitbucket
- Google Analytics & Tag Manager, SEO best practices

### LANGUAGES

- Romanian (Native)
- English (B2 Proficiency)